YOUTH DOCUMENTARY
OUR BELOVED SUMMER
Do you remember these two individuals
from an early summer ten years ago?
Kook Yeon-su really exhausts people.
Why does she live such an exhausting life?
Early birds just get tired earlier.
What is he going to be when he grows up?
We can sleep all we want when we're dead.
I'm sure he's going to be lazy
his whole life.
They were youthful 19 year-olds
who garnered national attention
and birthed so many memes.
Were they "loved" by people?
I enjoyed watching it too.
They were
extremely immature.
At first, I thought it was just Ung.
But if you think about it,
Yeon-su seemed more immature.
But to be honest,
they're both a mess.
Hey!
Kook Yeon-su! You are crazy!
Darn it!
I thought you were a ghost!
But in fact,
they weren't always bickering.
They grew on each other
since they were always together.
I could feel something else.
You know what it is, right?
That was what made it intriguing.
MORNING, AN ALLEYWAY IN HWIYEONG-DONG
You're three minutes late.
Just three minutes?
Three minutes is like
three years for us seniors.
Don't be ridiculous.
I now go to school
30 minutes earlier thanks to you.
Exactly.
I'm helping you save a lot of time.
Gosh, do we have
to walk to school together?
Hey.
No, thanks.
This isn't from me. It's from my mom.
Do you even have breakfast
if you go to school this early?
Thanks.
Hey.
Did you borrow volume three as well?
Yes.
Can you just let me read in peace?
I'm a speedy reader.
Can you let me read it first?
Maybe that's why
many people are wondering
how they're doing.
WILL WE GET TO SEE THEM AGAIN
AFTER 10 YEARS?
I doubt it'll be easy
to get them in front of the camera again.
A lot of time has passed.
And as you know,
they were never that cordial.
Now that I think about it,
the atmosphere was very tense.
I know for a fact that
they don't get along.
Hey. Let's do a retake.
I doubt it'll be easy.
WHAT'S YOUR IDEAL TYPE?
Someone who's very kind.
A petite and adorable girl
with a round face.
Someone who'll shower me with love.
Someone with whom I can always be--
How about just raising a dog?
I'm certain that the man I like
will be someone really incredible.
We spent that summer watching these two.
How are they doing now?
- Anyway…
- One thing I know for sure is that--
…I won't have to see
this annoying face again.
That's what I wanted to say.
EPISODE 12
BEGIN AGAIN
How did you first find out about it?
Well…
I can't remember that well.
But I think I just did.
The earliest memory I have
is probably of that day.
Every fall around this time, on this day,
my parents
always seemed very sad.
I didn't know back then.
I only found out later.
That's when I began having those dreams.
Dad.
Dad, where are you?
Dreams where I was abandoned repeatedly.
Dad.
In those dreams,
I couldn't see the face of the person
I was looking for.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Come on in.
- Ung. Hello.
- Gosh.
Come on in.
Are you hungry? Would you like a hotteok?
But I knew
- that I wasn't looking for
- Wait here.
- the parents I have now.
- Welcome.
That's all.
There's not much to it.
I was lucky to have been adopted
by such great parents.
Do they know?
That I know?
No. I didn't see the need to tell them.
You must have been lonely.
It must have broken your heart.
How did you endure it all by yourself?
I want to comfort you…
but I don't know how.
And I don't know what to say.
You've already comforted me.
What?
You're here by my side
and listening to my story.
That's enough.
Are you leaving already?
Don't worry.
I'll leave once you fall asleep.
Okay.
I really have trouble sleeping.
Yes.
But strangely enough,
I was able to sleep soundly…
when you were by my side.
Yeon-su.
- Ho!
- Hey, Chang-sik.
I thought you'd be back soon,
but you were closed for days.
I was bored to death.
Since we took some time off,
we decided to sightsee a bit.
What's gotten into you?
You don't even close during the holidays.
Just because. The weather was lovely.
You should have taken me along with you.
How could you go without me
when you knew I was alone?
You hurt my feelings.
Chang-sik.
Kids nowadays use this term,
"K.Y.P."
What's that?
It's short for "Know your place."
I see. So?
But you never stop butting in.
- What do you mean?
- Gosh, you're so slow-witted.
- Gosh.
- Mr. Choi.
Hey, Ji-ung.
- When did you return?
- We came back yesterday.
Hold on. Are you already going to work?
- No, I'm actually going home.
- What?
I need to get changed and head back.
- My gosh.
- Are you still filming?
I didn't get much screen time lately.
Don't you need me?
- Geez.
- We're done filming.
- We had our final shoot a few days ago.
- Good work.
I bet Ung was difficult to deal with.
Thanks for everything.
But why in the world are you filming Ung?
He's quiet and boring.
I'm sure Ji-ung has his reasons.
You really don't know your place.
Do you have any idea
how popular my son is?
I'm asking you. Do you?
Answer me.
Fine. You're so snappy.
Ji-ung. Now that you're done,
what will you be filming next?
If this is going to be aired on TV,
you should film my hardware store
and tell everyone
that we sell great tools.
Gosh, why are you hitting me?
Just ignore him.
You must be tired. Go home.
If you've been working until now,
does that mean you stayed up all night?
No, I slept a bit at work.
I'll let you know if I film
anything interesting again.
- Okay.
- I should get going then.
- Go on. Come by for a meal later today.
- I will.
Okay. Bye.
What a well-mannered kid.
He sure is different from your son
when their names are so similar.
You're still here?
Hey, what is it?
No, I'm fine.
I just came home to get changed.
No, have the meeting. I'll leave soon.
Bye.
Are you expecting a call from someone?
What? No.
Then hurry up and dig in.
Fine.
Watch out! It's dripping everywhere!
Wasn't it my phone?
No, it was mine.
What's the matter with her?
Grandma, I'm leaving now.
I can call him first. It's not a big deal.
What if he just fell asleep?
Or maybe he's still up.
What?
Why are you here?
When did you get here?
You should have called.
I was working. I just came.
Do you usually go to work at this hour?
I would have left sooner
had you told me you'd come.
Did you get some sleep?
No, I wasn't sleepy.
You need to stop staying up
all night just because you're not sleepy.
Have you been drinking jujube tea?
You should still try to sleep.
How can you sleep
when you're out and about?
You're going to take
sleeping pills again, aren't you?
I told you those pills
aren't good for you in the long run.
You may not quit cold turkey,
but you should--
Are you done?
I'm just saying you should've stayed home
and tried to sleep.
I'd rather be here right now.
What's that face? Are you happy or not?
I'm ecstatic.
Then you should've just said so
from the get-go.
Let's go. I'll drive you.
To work? I can take the bus.
It's quicker by car.
You can't drive
when you haven't slept a wink.
- That's--
- There you go again.
Fine, but at least
let me drive you to the bus stop.
Okay?
Okay. That's fine.
How can you nag me
every time I say something?
It's only because you keep worrying me.
I'm not a kid.
Exactly. So when will you grow up, Ung?
Then when will you grow up, Yeon-su?
Can you skip work today?
No way.
Come on. Just one day will be fine.
Work isn't like school. I can't do that.
You don't need to drop me off.
Just go home and sleep.
But you said I could.
I've changed my mind, so don't follow me.
Ung.
I have a question.
Are we dating again?
Did you think we weren't all this time?
I mean, I just wanted to be sure.
I thought it was obvious enough.
Ung.
I hope we get along.
He's so straightforward.
She's so adorable.
- Stop staring.
- Do you have good news or something?
- Why?
- I mean,
you've been coming here to eat often,
which is rare for you.
How was your trip?
Good. We also enjoyed
the autumn leaves on our way home.
We took a lot of photos too.
Look.
Look. Isn't it beautiful?
Yes, it is.
Resting for a few days
made me want to take a longer break.
Should we just close down for good
and enjoy our free time?
I've been telling you to do that.
Just rest and live off your S.C.C.
What is that?
"Son's credit card."
That sounds lovely.
You should have taken me with you.
To our trip?
Well, you don't really like
visiting the countryside.
And we thought you'd be busy.
It's okay.
I'm really fine,
so take me with you next time.
Okay. We will.
Hey, Ung.
I heard you're done filming
the documentary.
What do you say?
Isn't it about time
you returned to being our cashier?
Honey, Ung told me
to quit working and use my S.C.C.
S.C.C? What is that?
Do you not know?
It stands for "son's credit card."
What? Hey, son. What about me?
You should do something
that's even better and more popular.
What is it?
M.A.L.F.Y.
M.A.L.F.Y…
- Is that something better?
- Of course. It's much better.
"Making a life for yourself."
Thank you for the meal.
- Come by for dinner too.
- "Making…"
- I'll make dumpling soup.
- Don't tempt me with food.
That's the only way I can bring you here.
Hey, wait. "Making a…"
- Mr. Park.
- Hey, Intern.
- Where are your seniors?
- They're in a meeting with Ms. Lee.
How was the shoot?
We ended it with an interview of the cast.
Well…
What is it?
It was strange.
They didn't even look at each other.
No, not them.
Did anything interesting happen?
You know, with Chae-ran and Ji-ung.
Please don't ask about them anymore.
I don't think this is right.
- What did you say?
- And if this is because you think
they have feelings for each other,
then I definitely can't tell you anything.
I don't think it's right
to suspect your colleagues like that.
And why do you think something's going on
between Ms. Jung and Mr. Kim?
They're hardworking people
who are only focused on…
Ms. Jung.
Is this what you've been up to lately?
What do you mean? What's wrong?
Oh, him? He always stands there
and rambles on like that.
I thought he was just practicing
for some speech.
- Why are you here anyway?
- Sorry?
I was too lenient on you, wasn't I?
I always let you go home on time,
but I guess you had nothing better to do.
No, Ms. Jung. That isn't--
I'm going to set you straight, Intern.
No more going home for you.
Hello?
Ms. Jung, it's a misunderstanding.
- Hello?
- Mr. Park.
- Yes?
Are we ready?
Yes, sir.
Right. What was the last question again?
"What will you be doing
ten years from now?"
- Ji-ung, are you okay?
- What do you mean?
You didn't look well during the meeting.
You've been pulling all-nighters recently,
so just go home tonight.
- I'll wrap things up here.
- I'm fine.
You really don't look fine.
I think you should go home.
You could faint.
It's better to faint here than at home.
What?
Never mind.
I'll go home if I'm too exhausted,
so don't worry.
Look. You're running a fever.
This won't do. Get up.
- I'm really fine.
- I'm kicking you out. Go.
- Hey.
- Hurry.
- Go on.
I'm using this room tonight.
You can't come in.
What? What's going on?
Ji-ung's going home. He's running a fever
and might get us sick too.
- It's not that bad.
- What is it?
Is it a cold?
Go home, okay?
I suffered from a terrible flu last time.
Don't bother her, and just leave!
Take care, then.
Why is she overreacting all of a sudden?
Don't you think
she's just worried about you?
You're really slow-witted, aren't you?
Just go home.
Don't upset her.
What do you mean?
She hasn't been able to go home
since you've been pulling
all-nighters here.
I told her she could go home first.
Is she still
walking on eggshells around me?
Do you seriously think that's why?
Forget it. You're a lost cause.
How frustrating.
So frustrating.
This is terrible.
Gosh.
What's the matter with him now?
Gosh, that's hot.
Will you please focus?
We have so much to do.
They published the interview
you did last time.
Let's see.
They want to use
some of your drawings for the documentary.
Should I pick them out myself?
Or will you talk with Ji-ung about it?
What? Give it some thought.
By the way, I haven't seen him
since the shoot ended.
He must be busy.
Also, the gallery called.
You wanted to see
the night lighting, right?
They said you can come today.
Should we go?
No. Not today.
I have something to do.
What? Drawing?
Then Ye-in will be in charge
of the online marketing.
Ji-un, please help her.
- Okay.
I think you've all become too lax
after finishing a big project.
We still have
one more project left for this year.
So let's focus on that.
- Okay.
Good work. That'll be all for today.
Do you want to have dinner with me
after I get off work today?
I left my pen behind.
I can't today. Something came up.
Seriously? Didn't he ask me
to skip work this morning?
Is he upset?
Why?
What is it?
Don't tell me you're upset--
Okay.
This house never feels welcoming.
Just a second…
I'll just rest for a minute.
The person you have called…
Why are you here?
You have a fever.
It isn't that bad.
Right. It doesn't seem that bad.
When did you get here?
A while ago.
I had just looked up
how to medicate someone who's sleeping.
Oh, well. Take this.
Why does your house feel so empty?
You know I live here, right?
Why are you sick?
What kind of a question is that?
I mean, you've always been proud
of how healthy you were.
So I can't help but feel curious.
What did you do to get sick like this
and throw a pity party?
Nothing much.
I just pulled
a few all-nighters. That's all.
I'm going back to bed.
I won't see you out.
You must have
something you want to tell me.
I do.
But…
I'm not sure if I should
since you're sick right now.
Can I not hear it if I don't want to?
Yeon-su and I are dating again.
I guess I had no choice.
So? Why are you telling me this?
Because, just like when we were young,
I wanted you to be the first to know.
I got a girlfriend.
And just like then
I have nothing to say to you.
Should I congratulate you?
No, that's okay.
If you're done,
- can I go back to sleep?
- Yes.
One more thing.
Yes?
Can you please get lost?
Okay.
Hello?
Hey, are you up?
Yes.
I woke up a while ago.
I'm about to go out.
And you? Did you not sleep again?
No, I slept a bit.
Right. Did you have breakfast yet?
Have some breakfast and go to bed.
Okay.
Are you going to work?
Yes, I am.
I see.
That's right.
Well, what are you doing this weekend?
This weekend?
Yes, this weekend.
Do you want to hang out if you're free?
Let's see. This weekend…
If you're too busy, then it's okay.
No. I'm free this weekend. Let's meet.
Okay, then.
All right, then.
I should go to work now. I'm hanging up.
Okay.
Why does this feel so awkward?
Just be yourself, Yeon-su.
Darn it.
Maybe I shouldn't have asked to meet.
Gosh. It feels so awkward.
What are you doing?
- What?
- Aren't you going to work?
I am. I was just about to leave.
She's acting like she's caught some bug.
Hold on.
Maybe I did too.
I haven't talked to her
on the phone for so long.
Should I call her again?
No.
What is this? A water park?
My gosh!
Where's your head at?
Are you still half asleep?
This will be a pain to clean up.
Good luck.
- Hey, can you clean this up?
- What? But…
I didn't come here to clean.
Come on.
I'm your manager, not your servant!
I did ask him out first,
but he didn't seem that elated.
It didn't seem like
he was too excited to get back together.
So? Did he refuse to see you?
No, it's not that.
But it keeps bothering me.
It's as if I forced him
to hang out with me.
But you are seeing him.
Did you expect him to jump for joy?
You're not teenagers anymore, you know?
Still. It's not like him
to react that way.
He's definitely changed. It's weird.
Do you know what I find
the weirdest right now?
What?
The fact that you called me first.
You made the effort to call me
during work hours.
I'm not working right now. I'm driving.
You used to be a rude brat
who'd tell me to be brief
whenever I called you.
But you called me first,
and you're rambling on about Ung.
Well, that's because--
Okay. Who do you think has changed?
Who's the weirdest one here?
Anyway, stop worrying over
things like that. Just follow your heart.
It took you long enough
to get back together.
So can you please stop hesitating
and step up already? I'm hanging up.
Goodness. I can't believe I said that.
Hang up! Can you please hang up?
Gosh, that felt great.
What an adorable, little brat.
Gosh, why have I become so timid?
Has dating always been this difficult?
What did she want?
Ung and Yeon-su are going out again.
Are you serious?
Why did they go through all that
if they were going to get back together?
- How do you feel?
- What?
I know you don't really like him.
Gosh, my opinion doesn't matter.
She likes him, so what can I say?
That boy looks so sickly.
I'm sure he's fine.
But I am worried about his mental health.
He's a bit…
Never mind. Anyway, I'll keep
an eye on them. Don't you worry.
Or should I introduce her
to a few more men?
There are many wonderful candidates.
No, it's okay. Don't bother. Let her be.
Have this.
It's fine.
You must like him.
Not at all. Why would I like
that good-for-nothing?
Then take your time.
I should find her a good man
before I get any older and croak.
I don't have much time.
I have to see him again.
The building is quite huge
and there are many shops around here.
- Is it three stories tall?
- Yes.
It'd be nice if you give
this area a lot of exposure.
The sunset looks beautiful from up here.
Okay. I'll let them know.
Do you have any other requests?
I'm sure you'll do a great job.
Let me check the time.
You'll be able to see the sunset.
Take a look around with your colleague.
I'm here alone today.
I'll come by with them again next time.
What? I thought you came with him.
He's been here for a while.
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
I had forgotten…
What are you doing here?
…who I was in love with.
Are you here to see me?
Why did you want to meet on the weekend?
What?
I can't wait
that long.
Whether he changed or not doesn't matter.
Get back to work. I won't get in your way.
I didn't know about this place.
I could hold my exhibition here someday.
It was Ung.
I just loved him for who he was.
It won't take long.
Just wait a little while.
I was right.
The weekend was too far away.
This way.
There's an exhibition hall upstairs.
EDITING ROOM
Ji-ung, are you sure
you're feeling better?
Yes. You took my temperature earlier.
Did something good happen?
No.
Can we use a different insert?
Yes, we can. I'll find you one.
Thank you.
HOT AND SAVORY ROASTED CHESTNUTS
This feels like
we're on a date today.
It finally feels like
we're going out again.
It took a long time,
didn't it?
Darn these corn dogs.
- Can you hold this for me?
- No.
Okay, then.
- Do you want a corn dog?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- This looks tasty.
BEGIN AGAIN
Mr. Kim.
What was that? You just saw me.
- Were you just going to walk by?
- What brings you here?
You know I'm doing a special documentary.
Is Mr. Choi done with his documentary?
How's it going?
I'm really looking forward to it.
We're done shooting,
and we're editing now.
Are you going to use my footage too?
By the way,
is Mr. Choi very busy these days?
Is he still busy even after the shoot,
or is he just pretending to be?
I just can't seem to reach him.
Don't tell me that's your dinner.
That won't fill you up. Chi-seong.
Goodbye. Yes?
Am I done for today?
Yes. I thought
you were going to head home.
I'm going to have dinner with him.
Just you two?
What do you say?
I have some stuff to ask you anyway.
I was just going to have
a light meal while editing.
Are you that busy?
Well…
Now, tell me.
Explain the look
on your face from earlier.
What look?
When I said I couldn't reach Mr. Choi,
this was how you looked at me.
That's just how I look.
That's not true. I definitely saw it.
What is it? Tell me.
Has word got out
that Mr. Choi rejected me?
It seems like
you're the one telling people.
Then do they all know that
we're acting like the rumors are true?
You're the first person to tell me this.
Then do they also know
that Mr. Choi likes Ms. Kook?
I guess they do.
Could he not hide it better?
You knew?
They'll soon know
that the feeling is mutual.
You know a lot of things.
Do you want anything else?
Ma'am, can we get
a bottle of beer and soju?
Coming right up.
That's for me. You can order your own.
We can't be sober for this kind of talk.
How did you know that I'd be there?
Ye-in from your team told me.
Why did you contact her?
She contacted me first.
Why?
She was the only person
who asked if the scandal was true.
Oh, that.
I'm sure you already know,
but it was a false report.
Interesting, right?
All because I know a celebrity.
- But…
- Yes?
- …the photos were real.
- What?
I didn't know you were close enough
to go over to her house.
Hold on. I'm sure you could tell
from the photos,
but I didn't actually go inside the house.
Well, they can't take photos
of inside the house.
It's true. I was invited but I declined.
She invited you?
She also invited Eun-ho, I think.
So she invited you over to her place.
Is that important right now?
Well, it wasn't before.
But I'm not so sure now.
Hey.
- We're here.
- If you go now, things will be awkward.
Hey.
Look at you standing
in front of a woman's house again.
Hey.
Is this a new habit you picked up?
You've changed.
That's enough.
- Do you know what I hate right now?
- What?
We're not students anymore.
You don't have to go home so early.
Come back outside.
Come here.
It's too early to go home.
No. You can't go.
Who is that?
Is that you, Yeon-su?
Who in the world
is still out at this hour?
Would you like…
- to come over for some jujube tea?
- What?
I'm serious.
I want to get rid of…
I mean…
Let's have some together.
Pick it up. It's okay.
Or do you want to go see something lame?
I saw it coming,
so I wasn't that shocked.
The thing is,
I didn't see any harm in having a crush
since I never had one before.
But now that I do,
I feel motivated every morning
and I become hopeful
over the smallest things.
It makes me feel really special.
On top of that,
my imagination started going wild.
I even thought of becoming
a writer because of that.
I thought that was my calling.
This all came to me
after I started having a crush on him.
So how great is that?
No.
To be honest, it sucks.
How could he make me feel so miserable?
I feel like a worthless person
who came in between their precious love.
Do you get what I mean?
This is so wrong. I give up on my crush.
I take back what I just said.
I know.
Know what?
That I can't give up on him?
So annoying.
What? Don't get me wrong.
I'm not talking about you.
I'm talking about this lousy situation.
It gets better.
Having a crush on someone
is hard at first.
After a while,
it gets even worse.
Then…
it becomes unbearable.
But after that…
you get used to it.
Does that mean I'll be able to give up?
No.
You get used to the pain
that you eventually become numb…
and you get used to the heartache.
Then…
when does it stop?
Well…
I haven't thought of that.
Having a crush is so miserable.
Thank you
for helping me come to my senses.
The gallery at this hour? Isn't it closed?
It won't take long.
What? You have the key card?
Do you want to come in?
Is this where you'll be holding
your solo exhibition?
Yes.
I forgot what a great artist you were,
Mr. Choi.
But why did you have to come
and check at this hour?
I'm thinking of holding
a nighttime exhibition.
Late at night?
Yes. It'll last throughout the night.
I doubt many people will come
if it's too late.
Promoting your exhibition
won't be easy either.
That's why my idea keeps getting rejected.
Artists really do think differently
than us regular people.
But why at this hour?
Because it's when I drew them.
Plus…
it's when I'm always awake.
Just now,
I imagined the time you spent awake
alone at this hour.
It must have been lonely.
What goes through your mind
when you're drawing?
What do you think about
during that long period of time?
I'm not sure.
I never really thought about it.
But I couldn't have imagined
anything as perfect as this.
Every thin line that I drew…
Every second
that went by…
Every year…
Every moment…
Yeon-su was always there.
What did you imagine?
And continuously…
I will spend all of my time
loving Kook Yeon-su.
Let's go home.
Okay.
EPILOGUE
If there's an end to this crush,
I hope it's now.
Your fever's down. I'm leaving now.
I told you to leave earlier.
What now? Do you have something to say?
Hey, do you want to move in with me?
What?
Your place feels somewhat lonely.
Cut the nonsense and go already.
Thank goodness.
I was worried you'd say yes.
Rest up.
You should always sleep at home.
And that includes my place too.
I'm sick and tired of…
always being the bad guy.
BEGIN AGAIN
I want to keep living in this world.
Because misfortune always comes
disguised as happiness.
It's nothing.
Let's just ignore it.
I'm not going to be friends with you.
How are you going to end it?
But Ji-ung… Why aren't you looking at me?
I just don't get
why you're seeing Yeon-su again.
They say couples who fight
and break up often…
What are you doing, Yeon-su?
…have a higher chance
of breaking up again.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim